peoplespartyofcanada.ca 2019-11-18

# Privacy Policy - People's Party of Canada

**How we use your personal information**

Personal information (name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and other contact information) is used only to communicate with you, or to facilitate your participation as a volunteer. We take great care in the way we store and use it. The People’s Party of Canada (PPC) is a national organization, with a riding-based membership system; due to this your personal information may also be used by our local riding associations. As a registered federal political party, the PPC (including its Electoral District Associations and Riding Associations) is subject to regulation under the _Canada Elections Act_.

**Identification and unsubscribe information**

If you received a message from us, you are either: a PPC member, a recent donor or volunteer, you have recently taken action with one of our online tools, or you have an existing relationship with us. 

_To update or correct the information you provide to us_

, please send an email at [info@peoplespartyofcanada.ca](mailto:info@peoplespartyofcanada.ca). 

_To unsubscribe from our electronic messages or Newsletter_

, please click on the opt-out link at the bottom of the last email you received – or send an email at [info@peoplespartyofcanada.ca](mailto:info@peoplespartyofcanada.ca).

**Privacy statement**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. Security audits are periodically conducted to ensure the integrity of our systems.

**Sharing and Usage**

We do not share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone outside of the Party, without your permission or unless so ordered by a court of law. Information submitted is only available to PPC staff and EDA executives who manages this information for purposes of communicating with you on matters pertaining to PPC activities. These people received a series of guidelines on the use of data and are not allowed to share this information. If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments at [info@peoplespartyofcanada.ca](mailto:info@peoplespartyofcanada.ca).

 **Visiting our website**

When visiting PeoplesPartyofCanada.ca, your privacy is respected and protected.

Any information collected while you are visiting our website, such as server log data, is managed in accordance with this privacy policy and is protected by applicable law. Server logs include statistical information, such as visitors' IP addresses, time and duration of visits, and pages visited. These statistics may be used to improve your experience on PeoplesPartyofCanada.ca.

In addition, non-personal information may be collected through the use of cookies. Cookies are small text files maintained by your browser in order to remember user settings as you navigate sites. PeoplesPartyofCanada.ca uses cookies, for example, to remind your browser whether you chose to view our website in English or in French. You can also adjust your browser’s settings to refuse cookies, or to accept them on a case-by-case basis.

**Links to other websites**

Our website contains a small number of links to other websites. The PPC is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these websites.

 **Contacting Us**

Questions or concerns about our privacy policy or the information we collect may be directed to Yanick Villeneuve at the address: [yanick@peoplespartyofcanada.ca](mailto:yanick@peoplespartyofcanada.ca).

You can also contact us by phone at 819 205-2648, by fax at 819 205-2383 or by postal mail at the following address:

PPC Headquarters  
290, St-Joseph Blvd, office 205  
Gatineau, Québec  
Canada – J8Y 3Y3

**Spread the Word!**

Sign in if you'd like new recruits to be credited to you.
